http://www.lancasterfarmlandtrust.org/privacy-policy

What personal data we collect and why we collect it
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.lancasterfarmlandtrust.org. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website.
Lancaster Farmland Trust is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We only collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if
any.
Change/correct any data we have
about you.
Have us delete any data we have
about you.
Express any concern you have about
our use of your data.
Links
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information through our website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Lancaster Farmland Trust works with trusted third-party vendors to collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the Web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Surveys & Contests
From time-to-time our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 717-687-8484 or via email to info@lancasterfarmlandtrust.org.
You can make a difference.
donate now
stay up to date
Join our newsletter to keep informed about the latest news and events.
sign up
